[{"Title": "Edwin Poots to \u2018expedite\u2019 Irish language legislation for North", "URL": "https://www.irishtimes.com/news/politics/edwin-poots-to-expedite-irish-language-legislation-for-north-1.4584329", "Cards": [{"Question": "Who demands action on issue ahead of re-nomination of first minister Edwin Poots?", "Answer": "Edwin Poots"}, {"Question": "Who did Edwin Poots photograph?", "Answer": "Paul Faith"}, {"Question": "Who has pledged to implement Irish language legislation at Stormont as quickly as possible?", "Answer": "Edwin Poots"}, {"Question": "What was the name of the agreement that re-established powersharing last year?", "Answer": "New Decade, New Approach agreement"}, {"Question": "What has Stormont leaders agreed to convene a summit to tackle?", "Answer": "spiralling healthcare waiting lists in the North"}, {"Question": "What has Sinn F\u00e9in been pressing Mr Poots for?", "Answer": "introducing the cultural elements of the agreement"}, {"Question": "What is the name of the amendments to the Irish language legislation?", "Answer": "1998 Northern Ireland Act"}, {"Question": "What is the end of the current Assembly mandate?", "Answer": "end of the current Assembly mandate next spring"}, {"Question": "Who did Poots not specify a timetable?", "Answer": "Mr Poots did not specify a timetable"}, {"Question": "What does Edwin Poots believe in fulfilling all aspects of New Decade, New Approach?", "Answer": "I am committed to fulfilling all aspects of New Decade, New Approach"}, {"Question": "Who resigns as First Minister?", "Answer": "Arlene Foster"}]}, {"Title": "G7 ministers to discuss far-reaching deal on corporate tax", "URL": "https://www.irishtimes.com/business/economy/g7-ministers-to-discuss-far-reaching-deal-on-corporate-tax-1.4583263", "Cards": [{"Question": "Who is the managing director of the IMF?", "Answer": "Kristalina Georgieva"}, {"Question": "Who is set to discuss a deal on the reform of the global corporate tax system?", "Answer": "Hollie Adams/EPA Finance ministers from the main industrialised countries"}, {"Question": "What is the global minimum corporate tax rate for multinationals?", "Answer": "15 per cent"}, {"Question": "Who is the US treasury secretary?", "Answer": "Janet Yellen"}, {"Question": "What is the name of the OECD that calls for a major overhaul of corporate tax rules?", "Answer": "Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development"}, {"Question": "Who quoted the UK government as \"cautiously optimistic\" of a breakthrough at the G7?", "Answer": "Financial Times"}, {"Question": "What would be the aim of a deal on the reform of the global corporate tax system?", "Answer": "giving countries taxing rights on sales by major companies in their markets"}, {"Question": "What did the British finance minister Rishi Sunak say was a sign of?", "Answer": "\u2018Significant progress\u2019"}]}, {"Title": "Stephen Collins: What price Irish neutrality in today's world?", "URL": "https://www.irishtimes.com/opinion/stephen-collins-what-price-irish-neutrality-in-today-s-world-1.4583398", "Cards": [{"Question": "Who questioned the price Irish neutrality in today's world?", "Answer": "Stephen Collins"}, {"Question": "What is a wake-up call that we live in a dangerous world and cannot afford to be without allies?", "Answer": "cyberattack on our health system"}, {"Question": "Which web browser may be out of date?", "Answer": "The Irish Times Your Web Browser"}, {"Question": "What type of browser will not work properly?", "Answer": "Internet Explorer 9, 10 or 11"}, {"Question": "Which Google Chrome, Firefox, and Microsoft Edge are used for a better experience?", "Answer": "Google Chrome, Firefox or Microsoft Edge"}, {"Question": "The cyberattack on which Irish health service and the forced landing of a Ryanair flight in Belarus should prompt a fundamental reassessment", "Answer": "the Irish health service and the forced landing of a Ryanair flight in Belarus"}, {"Question": "What is the role of Irish neutrality in today's world?", "Answer": "Defence Forces"}, {"Question": "What is a long-outdated concept that suggests that this State doesn\u2019t take part in military alliance but has no particular view on the course of", "Answer": "Irish neutrality"}, {"Question": "When was Ireland neutral as between the fascist powers and the Allies?", "Answer": "second World War"}, {"Question": "What did Ireland decline to join in the Cold War?", "Answer": "North Atlantic Treaty Organisation"}, {"Question": "What was the reason for the decision to opt out of Nato?", "Answer": "refusal by the then government to recognise United Kingdom sovereignty over Northern Ireland rather than any objection to defending western democratic values"}, {"Question": "When did the State's top negotiator, TK Whitaker, make it clear that we would be prepared to join Nato", "Answer": "1961"}, {"Question": "Who said that if Europe was worth joining it was worth defending?", "Answer": "Se\u00e1n Lemass"}, {"Question": "What year did the government manage to avoid a firm commitment and retain a notional neutrality for fear of sparking opposition from the strong political lobby", "Answer": "a decade later"}, {"Question": "Where was the Irish version of neutrality possible?", "Answer": "geographical location in the western Atlantic between the United States and UK"}, {"Question": "What did the Irish version of neutrality provide?", "Answer": "security blanket"}]}]